Contact

+923448837231 (Mobile) adeelwaheed77@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/i-am-adeel-waheed (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

macOS

iOS

Machine Learning

Certifications

Freelance training certification
Registered Engineeer
Machine Learning
Python Course
Machine learning by Prof. Andrew
Ng

Adeel Waheed

| AL-HAMDULILLAH | Artificial Intelligence Engineer | AI & ML | Computer Vision | Pytorch | TensorFlow | CoreML | Data Scraping | Data Science | NLP/LLM | Python & C++ | HTML/CSS | Trying to heal the world |

Islāmābād. Pakistan

Summary

I have a great passion for enhancing my skills in the field of AI/ML. Expert in computer vision in different problem-solving environments. I have worked on so many projects related to computer vision using different machine-learning algorithms. Thanks to the Coursera platform from where I did many courses related to Machine learning for improving my skills.

Experience

SOFIT Consultancy (Private) Limited 2 years 5 months

Artificial Intelligence Engineer January 2022 - Present (1 year 6 months) Islāmābād, Pakistan

Data Trainer for Artificial Intelligence and Machine learning February 2021 - Present (2 years 5 months)

Islāmābād, Pakistan

Education

Hamdard University

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Electrical, Electronic and Communications Engineering · (2015 - 2020)